Before we really get started and talk about the phrases that we need to have a debate we should talk
在我们真正开始讨论我们需要辩论的短语之前，我们应该谈谈
about why we would have a debate one why is it useful for an English learner to practice this.
关于为什么我们要进行辩论，为什么对英语学习者来说练习这个很有用。
And two why is it useful in general to have a debate.
还有两个为什么一般来说进行辩论很有用。
Well the answer to the first question is if you have to debate you're not only for example giving a
那么第一个问题的答案是，如果你必须辩论，你不仅要给出一个
presentation and explaining an idea you have to listen to what other people say process that and then
演示和解释一个想法，你必须听别人说什么，然后处理
think very quickly of how to respond in a way that makes their side look weaker and your side looks
快速思考如何以一种让他们的一面看起来更弱而你的一面看起来的方式做出回应
stronger.
更强。
That's generally what a debate is all about.
这通常是辩论的全部内容。
You have to do it clearly.
你必须清楚地做到这一点。
You have to use everything that you know your ability to describe your ability to maybe express data
你必须使用你所知道的一切来描述你表达数据的能力
or technical details organize your thoughts.
或技术细节整理您的想法。
This can be very challenging.
这可能非常具有挑战性。
But by practicing this and I would recommend having debates as often as you can by practicing this you're
但是通过练习这个，我建议通过练习这个你可以尽可能多地进行辩论
going to really develop the ability to have quick conversations get back to people right away and have
将真正培养快速对话的能力 立即回复人们并拥有
a discussion where you have to engage your mind.
一个你必须全神贯注的讨论。
So it's a great way to actually practice your English language spoken English language abilities.
因此，这是实际练习您的英语口语能力的好方法。
But on the other side of that a debate is useful in many other many other situations many other cases.
但另一方面，辩论在许多其他许多其他情况下也很有用。
Imagine you have a company or you're in a company and you're going to launch a product launch a product
想象一下，你有一家公司，或者你在一家公司，你要推出一个产品，推出一个产品
and maybe there's a question about what feature to launch.
也许还有一个关于要启动什么功能的问题。
OK.
好的。
So let's say a feature is one of the things a product may have.
因此，假设功能是产品可能具有的功能之一。
OK let's say that if you add the feature let's call it feature a.
好的，假设如果您添加该功能，我们将其称为功能 a。
It's going to take two more months before the product can be launched.
该产品还需要两个月的时间才能推出。
And if you don't have the feature you can launch it right away but then it won't have the feature and
如果您没有该功能，您可以立即启动它，但它不会有该功能并且
maybe it's not as attractive to customers.
也许它对客户没有那么有吸引力。
So one thing you could do is set up a debate in maybe your team where you have two sides to people.
所以你可以做的一件事是在你的团队中进行一场辩论，在那里你有两个人。
Your job is to argue that we launch in two months with the feature.
你的工作是争辩说我们会在两个月内推出该功能。
Your job is to argue that we launch now without the feature and we will decide maybe or it will help
您的工作是争辩说我们现在在没有该功能的情况下启动，我们将决定是否可能会有所帮助
the person who is going to make the decision.
将要做出决定的人。
Decide soon faster or at least with a better understanding of the pros and cons of each side.
尽快做出决定，或者至少更好地了解双方的利弊。
So it can be a very very valuable thing having a debate in companies in groups sometimes even with friends.
因此，有时甚至与朋友一起在公司中进行小组辩论可能是一件非常有价值的事情。
OK.
好的。
So we can by having a debate maybe explore all possible avenues.
所以我们可以通过辩论探索所有可能的途径。
This is a common expression it means I don't know all of the possible ways that this thing can be done.
这是一个常见的表达方式，这意味着我不知道可以完成这件事的所有可能方式。
So I'm going to have a debate to help me figure out what possibilities there are to explore all possible
因此，我将进行一场辩论，以帮助我找出探索所有可能的可能性
avenues avenues are roads.
大道大道就是道路。
OK.
好的。
We may want to we may want to work out work out the kinks the kinks of an issue the Kinks a kink is
我们可能想要 我们可能想要解决问题的问题 问题的问题 问题的问题
something that's sort of a problem that may stick or cause other things to stick.
一些可能会粘住或导致其他东西粘住的问题。
So for example if you have a hose and there's a kink in it in the middle that means water cannot flow
因此，例如，如果您有一根软管并且中间有一个扭结，这意味着水无法流动
through it.
通过这。
So having a debate here might mean talking about in a debate format where the problems are and then
因此，在这里进行辩论可能意味着以辩论的形式讨论问题所在，然后
figuring out the best ways to resolve them.
找出解决它们的最佳方法。
Looking at both sides of it we can also as I mentioned before look at the pros and cons.
从它的两面来看，我们也可以像我之前提到的那样看利弊。
This is a very simple way to say the advantages and the disadvantages the good things and the bad things.
这是一种非常简单的方式，可以说好东西和坏东西的优点和缺点。
We often just say what are the pros and cons of this.
我们经常只是说这有什么好处和坏处。
What are the pros and cons of this.
这有什么好处和坏处。
It's a very common expression.
这是一个很常见的表达方式。
Well the pros are blah blah blah.
好吧，专业人士是胡说八道。
The cons are that.
缺点就是这样。
And we often need to explore these for example should we launch the product.
我们经常需要探索这些，例如我们应该推出产品。
What are the pros of that.
这样做有什么好处。
What are the cons of that.
那有什么坏处。
OK the debate format is great for that.
好的，辩论形式非常适合。
Now what's the difference between having a debate and having an argument.
现在辩论和辩论有什么区别。
I use the word make an argument for one side when I say that expression when I say to make an argument
当我说要提出论点时，我用“提出论点”这个词来表示一方
I could also be saying to make a case or to build a case that basically means to come up with things
我也可以说做一个案例或建立一个基本上意味着想出事情的案例
that support one side.
支持一侧。
It doesn't mean to argue in the way that we normally think of it an argument in most uses or most cases
这并不意味着以我们通常认为的方式进行争论，这是大多数用途或大多数情况下的争论
is two people fighting shouting at each other maybe throwing glasses of red wine at each other right.
是两个人打架互相大喊大叫，也许是互相扔红酒杯吧。
That's an argument OK usually but we can use argument in this way when we're talking about a debate
这通常是一个论点，但我们可以在谈论辩论时以这种方式使用论点
to make an argument to make a case for something when we want to express I believe this.
当我们想表达某事时，我相信这一点。
This is my view and I'm going to then make points that support this.
这是我的观点，然后我将提出支持这一点的观点。
I'm going to build a case for this.
我要为此建立一个案例。
This is my conclusion and my points are a b c and d.
这是我的结论，我的观点是 a b c 和 d。
This is my argument.
这是我的论点。
These are all the things I'm going to say to support this basic idea.
这些都是我要说的来支持这个基本想法。
So that's what we mean when we use the word argument or case when we're talking about a debate.
这就是我们在谈论辩论时使用论点或案例时的意思。
Now the last thing I want to mention before we get into the phrases for having a debate the last thing
在我们进入辩论的短语之前，我要提到的最后一件事是最后一件事
I want to mention is this interesting thing which we call the Devil's Advocate now the devil's advocate
我要提的是这个有趣的东西，我们现在称之为魔鬼代言人
basically means it's a role the person who always disagrees or says the opposite.
基本上意味着这是一个总是不同意或说相反的人的角色。
As a way to explore or force you to think about things in another way.
作为一种探索或强迫你以另一种方式思考事物的方式。
So if you say I want to start a new business and I'd like to start maybe a convenience store then I
所以如果你说我想开一家新公司，我想开一家便利店，那么我
say well what about all of the other convenience stores in the neighborhood.
说好附近所有其他便利店的情况。
There are so many there's a lot of competition.
有这么多，有很多竞争。
Have you thought about that and maybe that person says so why are you.
你有没有想过，也许那个人会说你为什么会这样。
You should be excited about my idea.
你应该对我的想法感到兴奋。
Why are you disagreeing with me.
你为什么不同意我的观点。
Hey I'm just playing playing devil's advocate.
嘿，我只是在扮演魔鬼的拥护者。
That means I'm just trying to help you explore why you have this opinion and whether or not it's the
这意味着我只是想帮助您探索为什么您有这种观点以及它是否是
right view to have.
正确的看法。
I'm helping you so this is kind of a role and when you're having a debate sometimes you need to play
我在帮助你，所以这是一种角色，当你进行辩论时，有时你需要扮演
devil's advocate as a way to explore the other side.
魔鬼的拥护者作为探索另一面的一种方式。
Maybe you both agree with the same side.
也许你们都同意同一方面。
In fact right.
事实上对。
Well the devil's advocate role can allow you to figure out what both sides are at least.
那么魔鬼代言人的角色可以让你至少弄清楚双方是什么。
So it's an interesting it's an interesting role to play.
所以这是一个有趣的角色。
I really like playing devil's advocate when I have debates either with my colleagues or when I have
我真的很喜欢在与同事辩论或与同事辩论时扮演魔鬼的拥护者
debates with my friends.
和我的朋友辩论。
Sometimes I'll take the opposite view that I actually have.
有时我会采取与我实际持有的相反的观点。
Just for fun just to see if I can make an argument for that.
只是为了好玩，看看我是否可以为此争论。
It's fun.
好有趣。